maxoffsky.com 2013-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Maxoffsky |

This application (hereinafter “Application”) collects some Personal Data from its Users.

The Data are collected and processed for the purposes set out below.

## Data Processing Ownership

Maxoffsky – Placentia, CA, 92870,  
msurguy@gmail.com

## Kinds of Data

The Data that may be collected by this Application are: Cookie, Browsing and usage Data, Email, First Name and Last Name.

The Personal Data may be freely inserted by the User or the Data Subject, or collected automatically when using the Application.  
Any use of Cookies by the Application or the owners of third party services used by the Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify the User and remember his/her preferences for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data, in particular Navigation Data, by deactivating the Application’s Cookies may make it impossible to surf or for the Application to provide its services.

The Personal Data collected may regard both the User and third parties whose data the User provides.  
The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through the Application and declares that (s)he has the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Owner of all responsibility towards third parties.

## Mode and place of processing the Data obtained

### Method of Processing

The Data Controller processes the Data of the Interested Parties and Users in a lawful and proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data. Processing is carried out using computers and / or telematic means, with organizational methods and logics strictly related to the stated purposes.  
In addition to the owner, in some cases, access to the Data may be available to external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies). The updated list of Managers may be requested from the Owner at any time.

### Place

The Data are processed at the headquarters of the Data Controller, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document.

### Conservation Time

The Data are kept for the time necessary to perform the service requested by the User, and the User can always ask for their suspension or removal.

## The use of the collected Data

The Data concerning the User or the Data Subject are collected for the following purposes: Analytics, Interaction with external social networks and platforms and Email contact.

The kinds of Personal Data used for each purpose are given in the specific sections of this document.

The use of Data for additional purposes by the Owner, may in some cases, and for legal purposes, require specific consent by the User or the Data Subject.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data and the services provided by third parties

  * ### Analytics

  * ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

  * ### Email contact

## Additional information about data processing

### Legal Protection

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner of the Application in court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from its improper use or that of related services by the User.

### Additional Information

Specific information may be shown on the pages of the Site concerning particular services or the processing of Data provided by the User or by the Data Subject.

### Maintenance

The User’s Personal Data may be further used in ways and for purposes required for Application maintenance.

### System Logs

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services it uses may collect system logs, i.e., files that record interaction – including navigation. They may also contain personal data, such as IP addresses.

### Information not contained in this policy

More information on processing Personal Information may be requested from the Owner at any time.

### The Rights of Data Subjects

Those persons to whom the Data refer have the right, at any time, to know whether their data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Owner of the Processing System.

The following two tabs change content below.

  * Bio
  * Latest Posts

Maks is young and energetic guy who lives in LA area with his wife and works in IT industry. He is well-versed in three languages (English, Russian, Ukrainian) and a dozen of programming languages. Oh, and he also is a breakdancer!
